Previously on 10 Things I Hate About You...
I think we shouldgive it a shot.
I do, too.
Is that what this is?
Your master plan to get meto sleep with you?
I love you, Bianca.
Oh, my God. I love you, too.
Just because I want to have sexdoesn't mean I should.
I've been fooled by guyslike you before,
but not his time.
I'm on The Biggest Poser.
I leave for New York tomorrow.
I miss my boyfriend.
Joey left two days ago.
I can still smellhis body spray.
That's becauseI'm wearing it.
To remember him.
He's not dead.
He's just on a reality TV show,
which is probably worse.
At leastthere's dignity in death.
Could you showa little compassion?
This is his locker.
We shared so many kisses here.
Here's a novel idea--why don't you call him?
Then he can listen to thisinstead of me.
I can't. He's sequesteredin the model house,
and they only have one phone.
Last night, some girltold Joey to hang up
or she'd scratch his face.
I'd give anything to hearthe sound of his voice.
The Buddha says, "Desire isthe root of all suffering."
Thanks, fortune cookie.
Is that supposedto make me feel better?
The fact that you wantJoey to call
is creating the painyou're feeling right now.
So what? I shouldn'twant him to call me?
Exactly.
So you're not dyingto talk to Patrick
about the other night?
If I wanted to talkto him about it,I'd call him.
He's not in a model house.
I'm walking my path,and he's walking his.I wish him well.
You're so deluded.
Whoa, wait a second.
Why is Dad talkingto Miss Tharp?
Maybe he's worriedyou're an android.
Oh, my God, they're dating.
♪ Hey, hey ♪
Bianca, calm down.
Try and imagine we're bamboogently bending in the wind.
And hurricane Tharpis about to rip us to shreds.
We don't know they're dating.
Maybe they were reminiscingabout your fake intervention.
I am an experton flirty body language.
She didthe hair flip/arm squeeze
which means they've beenon two dates
and they've made outwith tongue.
What are we going to doabout this unholy union?
We support Dad.
We've been wanting himto date for years, remember?
Someone age-appropriatewho works at the hospital,
not the crazy lady from schoolwith zero boundaries.
Dad's coming.
If you say anything,I will hurt you.
I thought Buddhistswere nonviolent.
I'm a beginner.
Hi, girls.
Hi, Daddy.
Hi, Dad.
How was your day?
Uneventful.
Yep.
They ran this guy's shortsup the flagpole at lunch.
That was funny.
And then we saw youflirting with Miss Tharp.
Bianca.
She thinks you two are dating.
What? That's absurd.
All right, I'm not goingto lie to you.
We've been on two dates.
Told you.
I'm sorry I didn'ttell you sooner,
but I wanted to wait till Iknew it was something special.
See, Bianca?It's nothing special.
Actually, it is.
Or it could be.I don't know.
She's funnyand surprising and--
20 years younger than you
and our guidance counselorand a weirdo.
She's different,and I like her.
And when I'm around her,I feel alive again.
You know how, like,when your foot goes asleep
and you shake itand it gets tingly?
[chuckles]
Ew, now you're bringingfeet into this?
Girls, you know you're
the most important thingsin my life.
I won't date Miss Tharpif you tell me not to.
Okay, then don't.
All right.
I'll just be really sad.
But that's okay
because your happinessis more important than mine.
Dad, we would never dreamof doing something so selfish.
Would we, Bianca?
[sighs]
Why don't youinvite her over for dinner
so that we can getto know her better?
Really?
[phone rings]
Oh, it's Darlene.
Should I let it ringone more time
and not be too eager?
Or what if she hangs up?
Darlene, are you there?
Oh, hi. Nothing.
[gong]
And breathe...
in through the right nostril
and out through the left.
[gong]
Everyone, slowly returnfrom nothingness.
Now, I knowour meditation collective
has no official leader,
but I havea few announcements.
First of all,welcome, Kat Stratford.
Kat,
we're excited to bea part of your journey.
Namaste.
[Man]Namaste.
Second, there are stilla few spots open
on our study abroad tripto Nepal.
Anyone else like to join us?
I'm in.
Wonderful. I'll get youthe paperwork.
[phone rings]
Oh, my God, Joey,I miss you so much.
I miss you more than my mom.
I can't wait to hear aboutall your modeling adventures,
but first,I have to tell you
about the insanityI'm dealing with.
My dad is datingMiss Tharp.
No way.
Nice job, Dr. Stratford.
Joey, this is not good news.
Old people settle down fastso that they won't die alone.
What if she becomesmy stepmom?
Calm down, Bianca.Here's what you should do.
I have to call my baby girlbefore bedtime.
Joey?
Joey, are you there?
[sighs]
Why do they only haveone phone?
Okay, come on.You can do it.
Swim upstream, little salmon.
Is there any way I canpersuade you to keep moving?
I think we bothknow the answer to that.
What's this?
It's an inviteto my little sister'sbirthday party.
Princess theme.She asked me to--
All right, it's a love poemfor Dawn, okay?
[laughs]
Did you write itin calligraphy?
So what if I did?
Look, last night
on the phonewithout thinking,
I said, "I got to getsome Z's, Dawn,"
but I don't knowif she was done talking.
Now I feel horrible.
So I wrote her a poemto apologize.
For saying good night?Nice backbone.
Well, better to tell Dawnhow I feel
than let her get away.
That's the moralof every romantic comedy.
There. Now she'll knowhow I feel in iambic pentameter.
Sorry.
What a lovely home.
Thank you.
It's so inviting.
It's like I'mon the set of Friends.
[both laugh]
Jennifer.
Bianca, you love Friends.
Why don't you discussthis shared interest
while I check the lasagna?
[both chuckle]
Hey, did you hear Friends got canceled?
Yes, but people love itin reruns.
And you knowwhy I think that is?
Urban tribes are nowa substitute
for traditional families.
Yeah, plus it's funny.
I'm sorry I'm late.I was meditating.
Dad, can I talk to youabout an amazing opportunity?
Kat, I have no interestin a timeshare right now,
especiallywhen we have a guest.
Oh, hi, Miss Tharp.
Namaste.
Namaste, Kat.
Dad, I want to go to Nepal.
And I'm suresomeday you will.
How about next week?
Huh?
There'sa school sanction program
where I'd spend three monthsin a remote village
in the Himalayashelping them build a school.
Plus, the trip is ledby university faculty members
who'll teach coursesin East Asian history.
And the best part--
daily mediation at a monastery
with real Buddhist monks.
That soundslike the perfect trip
for someone else's daughter.
Let her go. I'll turnher room into a gym.
I know that program, Walter.It's very well run.
Not onlydo the students achieve
a higher levelof consciousness,
but it looks greaton a college application.
Don't say no yet.Just think about it.
I will.
After dinner. Would youtake a seat, please?
[Bianca]So, Miss Tharp,
have you ever been married?
Bianca, what kindof a question is that?
No, it's okay, Walter.I want this to be an open forum
where we can allshare our truths.
Great. So have you?
I have been engagedthree times--
four if you countthis one night in Vegas.
But I haven't actuallyquite made it down the aisle.
Oh, why not?
Bianca.
Well, it's a questionI am currently trying
to figure out in therapy.
Enough questions.This is a family dinner,
not a deposition.
Dad, I'm just trying to hearMiss Tharp's truth.
So have youever been arrested?
[Walter and Kat]Bianca!
What?
Yes, but I wasyoung and naive.
Girls, please learnfrom my mistake.
If a cute man asks you to carrya package over the border,
don't do it.
Don't ever dowhat cute men want,
unless it's me.
[all chuckle]
[phone rings]
Oh, my God, Joey?
Babe, I've been missing--
Give that back, Dad.
Bianca, we havea dinner guest.
You can talk to Joey later.
No, I can't.
You just sit there and bepolite or go to your room.
[phone rings]
I've been waiting for himto call all day.
You're ruining my life.
Darlene, I'm sorry.
Bianca can bea bit over-dramatic.
A bit? It's like she'sliving in a telenovela.
[laughs]
Let's not let it ruin our meal.
[knock on door]
May I come in?
I don't mean to be rude,
but I don't wantto share my truth
or do mirror workor do any of that crap.
I just want to be alone.
I can tellhow much you miss him.
I love him.
And he's gone.
And who knowswhen the model phonewill be free again.
Oh, I remember what itfeels like to be your age
and in love.
His name was Diego.
When he got deported,I thought my life was over.
And the worst part about it--nobody took my pain seriously.
They're so insensitive.
I'm sure they'redoing their best,
but not everybody's equippedto give us what we need.
I'm here.
I'm a good listener.
Thanks, Miss Tharp.
Oh, please call me Darlene.
So how long have you guysbeen together?
We've been togetherfor about two months.
Okay, Darlene, here I come.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, my God, I can't believewe're wearing the same thing.
You look so cute.
So do you.
♪ Stumble out of bed ♪
♪ Get a lookthat&apos;ll knock &apos;em dead ♪
♪ It&apos;s Friday,got nothing to wear ♪
♪ My favorite jeansare starting to tear ♪
♪ It&apos;s looking likea perfect day ♪
♪ For us to get together ♪
♪ We&apos;ll drive in my car ♪
♪ We&apos;ll go as we are ♪
♪ Hustle and bustle away ♪
Here. I made yousome Nepalese tea.
Or chaia,as the Sherpas say.
Katarina, I'm not goingto give you my blessing
to go halfwayaround the world--
Correction.Only 12,130 kilometers,give or take a few.
Oh, is that all?
I didn't realize you couldcome home on weekends.
I know it's far,
but this isan amazing opportunity.
And I'll be going offto college in 18 months.
Consider thisa dress rehearsal.
For a play I don't want to see.
I'm ready for this.
Please don't keep me fromgoing because you're scared.
I'm not scared.I'm terrified.
Of what?
Of what?You're going to a place
without indoor plumbingor telephones
or parental supervision.It's dangerous.
Some warlord's going to payseven goats for you.
Seven goats?
Yes.
Dad, you can just say no.You don't have to insult me.
Ha.
Please let me go.
Let you?
I've never let youdo anything in your life.
It's always been oneof my favorite thingsabout you.
Are you sayingwhat I think you're saying?
Please don't celebratetill you're alone in your room.
All right.
Thanks, Dad.
And don't come backwith one of those ringsthrough your nose.
[phone vibrates]
[whispering]Hey, Joey, I'm in class.
[whispering]Oh, okay, good news.
I made it to fourout of my six "go sees."
Oh, that's so--
Oh, goody,a bejeweled cell phone.
Just what I always wanted.
But, Mr. Meanly,it's a matter of life or death.
[chuckles]
[snoring]
Hey.
Hey back.
That's a really good lookfor you.
Thanks. I got itfor my trip to Nepal.
I leave next week.
For three months.
It's this fascinatingstudy abroad program.
Cool.
Have fun.
You, too.
[Dawn]Your poem isthe most romantic thing
any guy's ever done for me.
Even that time Chris Yu
scratched my nameon his guitar.
I just wanted you to knowI couldn't live without you.
Aw, recite it to me again.
Hark, my Dawn.
You are the sweetest treatin the candy store.
I've tasted your sugar,and I want some more.
You're so hotyou melt my heart.
Lips, sweet and delicious,like a mixed fruit tart.
You're cuter than Bambi,an adorable baby fawn.
You light up my days,
my very own Dawn.
Oh.
Check out allthat natural beauty.
Eyeball exploding, right?
You guys are infor the journey of a lifetime.
Maybe even a few lifetimes.
[all laugh]
That's a littleBuddhist humor.
Sindu, that is too funny.
I find your spirit infectious.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Do you know our host families?
I'd like to start practicingpronouncing their names.
The families livein one-room huts.
It's a little crowded,
so we'll be sleeping in tents.
But it'll be spring,so you know what that means.
It won't be too cold?
Avalanche season.
But don't worry.
You'll eachhave a GPS tracker.
I haven't lost a student yet.
Just a toe.
Now, let's talk vaccinations.
You'll need hepatitis A and B,typhoid, and tetanus,
but good news,
because of the new wellwe dug last quarter,
you'll no longer need theJapanese encephalitis booster.
One thing we can't vaccinateagainst is dysentery.
[sighs]
I really wish we could,though.
But we can't. Questions?
It's a non-invasive process
that will really help youaccess your--
I hate to interrupt,but this is an emergency.
Oh, okay, just give mea sec, Tanya,
and then we'll startthe hypnosis.
Hey, what is going on, honey?
Joey calledduring math class,
and Mr. Meanly tookmy phone away.
Darlene, please help meget it back.
Bianca, honey, in this office,I'm not Darlene.
I'm Miss Tharp.
And Miss Tharp hasto support Mr. Meanly.
You should not be talkingon the phone during class.
But you know how hard it's beenfor me to not talk to Joey.
Yesterday you called usstar-crossed lovers.
And Darlene wasserious about that.
Really?
Because it sounds likeshe was just sucking up to me
so she could date my dad.
No, she would never do that.
In fact, if you wantto process this tonight
over a pint of ice creamand a Katherine Heigl movie,
Darlene will be there.
Tell Darlene I said"Thanks for nothing."
[Walter]Bianca, be reasonable.
I am being reasonable, Dad.
She's the one withmultiple personality disorder.
Darlene said you werejust upset
because she wouldn'tgive you your phone back.
I'd hardly call thata severe mental illness.
This isn't about my phone.
It's the fact that she's
my guidance counselorand your girlfriend.
It's too confusing.
All right, why don't wejust invite her over?
And we'll share our truths.
After all , if there can be
a lasting peacein Northern Ireland
I'm sure we can work this out.
Dad, you don't get it.
I don't want to work this out.
Now, please just leave meto my homework.
Bianca, wha--
It's too strange.
You said if we didn't want youto date her, you'd stop.
So stop.
Okay, fine.
See you in ournext class, okay?
Siena, hey.
Hi.
Listen, I haven't beenable to find
quick-drying snow pantsanywhere.
Where did you get yours?
Oh, Kat, I didn't tell you?
I'm not going to Nepal.
You're not?
I realizedI don't like hiking,
which means I'll probablyhate trekking.
But have fun.Take pictures.
Hey.
Hey back.
I'm glad I caught youbefore you left for Nepal.
Really?
Why?
Keith found thisin the back of his van.
I know how much you like it.
Thanks.
I was wondering where it was.
In Keith's van.
Yeah, you said that.
I guess I'll see you around.
Have a safe trip.
Joey, I miss you so much.
I miss you more.
Co Liviette just faintedduring our photo shoot,
so we have the phoneuntil she revives.
Then she's going to wantto call her baby.
Oh, goody, I hopeshe's out for a while.
We have so much to catch up on.
Tomorrow's makeover day.I'm so nervous.
What if they shave my head?
I don't knowhow to work my skull.
Joey, there's somethingI have to do right now.
Call me back later, okay?
But--
Love you. Bye.
[sighs]
[Man on TV]I'm on the other end.
Yo, Tom, I thoughtyou brought it.
You've got style.You were sexy.
Looks good. Can I have some?
Don't choke on it.
Look.
I'm sorry I freaked outabout Darlene.
I was being selfish.
Was?
You mean you're not beingselfish anymore?
Listen, I know how it feels
to want to talkto someone so badly it hurts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.Can I call her?
Yeah, but...
I'm switching to the otherguidance counselor.
Deal.
[phone rings]
Joey.
Don't worryabout your makeover.
I told youshe'd come around.
Listen, are you free to seea movie this weekend?
I have seen you model enoughto know you're a chameleon.
What are you doing out here?
The program recommends
we try out all our equipmentbefore the trip.
Can I ask you something weird?
Where will you goto the bathroom up there?
Oh, God.
You're so brave, Kat.
I could never go to someplacehalfway around the world
where I didn't know a soulor speak the language
or have any ideawhat I'm eating,
but it all soundsso exciting and exotic.
I don't want to go.
I like indoor plumbing.
I don't wantto forage for roots
or wear snow pants.
And--
And what?
And he didn'ttry to stop me.
I'm stopping you.
I need you here.
Dad is still datingour guidance counselor,
and based ontheir body language,
they're three dates awayfrom having sex.
♪♪ [vocalizing]